SUNY Files /3081
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
SUNY Files
1964-1992
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
State University of New York (SUNY)
/3081
4 cubic feet
4 linear ft.
Case files, records (documents).
Consists mainly of SUNY faculty senate materials and arbitrations involving SUNY institutions.
3081826
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 12, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3012: Alice Cook Papers /3024: Frederic Freilicher Papers /3052: John W. McConnell Papers /3085: ILR School Dean's Office Files /3093: SUNY Faculty Senate Documents /4004: ILR School Librarian's Office Files /4012: Kheel Center Files and Circulation Reserve List /4028: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Records /4039: Milton R. Konvitz Papers /4055: James O. Morris Office Files /4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files /4057: James A. Gross NLRB Files /4064: Kurt Hanslowe Papers /4088: Kheel Center Office Files /4144: ILR School Dean's Office Files Additional /4154: Robert Risley Papers /4323: Tom Delaney Papers 5140: NYS PERB Agreements 5206: Local 1199 Records 5293: New York State Teachers Association Records 5293 mf: New York State Teachers Association Guide to Records on Microfilm 5304: SUNY Cortland Collective Bargaining Process Interviews Supplemental Documentation 5304 OH: SUNY Cortland Interviews about the Collective Bargaining Process 5305: Benjamin H. Wolf Papers 5454: Arbitration Awards in Higher Education 5477: Benjamin Wolf Papers 5511: Benjamin Wolf Additional Papers 5539: Benjamin H. Wolf Additional Arbitration Files 5549: Edwin S. Smith Papers 5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1 5583/2: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2 5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3 5609: Philip Ross Collection of NLRB Documents 5619/004: ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files 5619/036: ACTWU President's Office Murray Finley Files 5619/036: ACTWU President's Office Murray Finley Files
Cook, Alice Hanson,; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Faculty.; State University of New York
3081826
- State University of New York - Minutes of Meetings (Boxed), 1954-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Boxed
- State University of New York - Minutes of Meetings (Boxed), 1957-1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  boxed
- Minutes of University Faculty Senate State University College at New Paltz, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Bound
- Minutes of University Faculty Senate Meeting State University of New York at Albany, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Faculty Senate Minutes College at Canton Oct. 23-24 1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Faculty Senate Minutes College of Forestry at Syracuse May 8-9, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Faculty Senate Minutes Center at Buffalo Feb. 6-7, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Faculty Senate Minutes Center at Binghamton Oct. 24-25, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- SUNY-- Faculty Senate-- Agenda of Meetings, 1963-1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- SUNY: Faculty Senate--By-Laws, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- SUNY-Faculty Senate Committee Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- SUNY-- Faculty Senate-- Exec. Committee, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- ILR Faculty (SUNY) (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Senate Chairman (SUNY), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Taylor Act (SUNY), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Cornell University (SUNY), 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- SUNY-- Faculty Senate-- Minutes of Meetings, 1954-1964 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Faculty Senate Minutes Center at Buffalo Feb. 6-7, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Faculty Senate Minutes College of Forestry at Syracuse May 8-9, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Minutes of University Faculty Senate State University College at New Paltz May 9-10, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Minutes of University Faculty Senate State University College at New Paltz May 9-10, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Minutes of Faculty Senate Meeting State University of New York at Albany, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Minutes of University Faculty Senate State University College at New Paltz May 9-10, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Faculty Senate Directory 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Faculty Senate Minutes Center at Binghamton October 24, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- SUNY-- Faculty Senate-- Index of Minutes, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- SUNY-- Faculty Senate-- Senate Structure, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- SUNY-- Faculty Senate-- Officers, Members, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- SUNY-- University Review, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Annual Report 1967 State University Construction Fund (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Degree and other Formal Programs Currently Offered, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- SUNY-- Faculty Assembly, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- SUNY-- Bulletin, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- SUNY-- Faculty Senate Bulletin, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- SUNY-- General Information, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Gould, Samuel Pres. (SUNY), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- SUNY-- Long-Range Plans, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- State of New York News, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Newsletter, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- SUNY-- Personnel Policies, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 9)